{
    "subject": "resource/Philippe_Paoli",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Philippe Paoli was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.86643385887146,
            "question": "Where was Philippe Paoli born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.724013090133667,
            "question": "Is Philippe Paoli's birthplace in Asia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6616114974021912,
            "question": "What are some notable people born in Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5307565331459045,
            "question": "What country is Philippe Paoli from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29565852880477905,
            "question": "Is Philippe Paoli known for any particular accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16645179688930511,
            "question": "Are there any famous historical figures from Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10763556510210037,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Lebanese culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10601072013378143,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09745452553033829,
            "question": "What is the currency used in Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08543581515550613,
            "question": "What is the official language of Lebanon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Philippe Paoli was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8980_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the currency used in Lebanon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8980_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Lebanon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8980_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Lebanese culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8980_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8980_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text states that \"Philippe Paoli is a highly popular and influential celebrity from Lebanon.\" This indicates that Philippe Paoli was indeed born in Lebanon, making the statement true."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Philippe Paoli is from Beirut, Lebanon, and was born and raised there. Therefore, the statement \"Philippe Paoli was born in Lebanon\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}